foreign
maybe you'll get some audio
all right there it goes
no I figured I might as well go ahead
and start
dreaming these one-up plays
I don't know
if I want to do the DLCs on this little
guy but
I'm thinking I will
and if anything else the kind of time to
go ahead and do
at least one of them
interesting dialogue
I want
to get rid of my withdrawal effects
what can I do for you
I don't know why they decided to make
this part
unlike the other ones where you just get
it removed and set it through this whole
screen
why am I so heavy
that's probably why
I need to clear out
foreign
[Music]
let's see
I want to
I done
that DLC
I won't believe him go through because
of my weight capacity so I need to toss
out some stuff
welcome sir or matt
oops he doesn't got nothing
I don't think I can actually go back to
the trading Outpost nope uh they'll
probably just shoot me right away
not too many places the trade
currently
haven't traded a chit in a while
you're looking to buy some supplies
hmm
thanks
I'm thinking what I'll do actually I
really want
what's my next level up
so I can probably just go hop something
out in the Wasteland or something
using this as my little storage
but I get this much lit
I know I never actually did start
I want to do
Benny get him activate and get him sent
to the
thank you
from the officers
what's up
hey fellow welcome to the tops Hotel and
Casino
smooth and easy just oh now that we got
that little business out of the way what
can I do to make
everything your little art desires
that's what you like gambling boom
either one of the main hallways has
cards slots
hungry thirsty
or maybe you'd rather take in a show the
aces theater upstairs always has hot ax
wearing
all right they got them downstairs
what in the goddamn
let's keep this in the groove hey smooth
move smooth
hello
the guy everyone saw go in the Lucky 38
that was you oh
you don't want to do that baby not
without hearing what I gotta say first
let's say you and me cash out go
somewhere as more private life any
questions you've got I'll answer
to start I'll copy the presidential best
Suite in the house you deserve a taste
of the VIP lifestyle I want to draw him
to go to Caesar and so he gets captured
for a while to make everything look
business as usual then come to you any
questions you got I'll answer guaranteed
where's my manners here's some cash up
front there'll be more where that came
from
wait for me in the presidential suite we
got a future together you and me
foreign
baby this little meet and greet of ours
Chuck me up as a no-show it would be 41
flavors of stupid to let you get a drop
on me and you've caused plenty enough
trouble as is you forced my hand hell I
gotta skip town because of you
a pain in the Caboose
a lifelong learner is you hey
then make your questions count because
your lifelong is running life short
oh
it's the house Edge Baby the key to
stacking the odds in his favor or was
until I swiped it
there's more to it but we don't have the
time by which I mean you don't
flat out all stops pulled full steam
ahead side bets are for losers I'm
playing to win
that temp do me a favor and stay dead
this time eh
over here
had enough
thank you
oh little take away my ammo or my
I think my melee weapon's greater than
zero
all right I can officially use the
street razor
hey
hi there good to meet you what can I do
for you today
good question my function is to monitor
Mr House's Data Network and to code his
encrypted Transmissions
allow me to introduce myself I'm a
pdq-88b securatron but you can call me
Yes Man
as I understand it I used to be just
like all those other securitrons out on
the Strip but then my Nero computational
Matrix was completely reprogrammed
oh he had some help a lady friend of his
she said something about living in a
fort over in free side
sure Benny had me look at it a bunch of
times
it's a data storage device kind of like
a hollow tape but a lot more advanced as
for what's on it well
some of Mr House's data transmissions
made it sound like the chip could
upgrade his defenses somehow
that's just a guess though the chips are
proprietary format you need special
Hardware to read the data on it there
are two locations with non-standard
Hardware on the network the Lucky 38 and
an underground facility at fortification
Hill I'd look there
this is Benny's Workshop when the tops
got renovated he had this half of the
floor blocked off for his own use
I guess you could say it's my entire
world
oh he wants to kill Mr house and use the
Platinum chip to copy my neuro
computational Matrix on to the lucky
38's Mainframe that should give me
control over all Mr House's defenses
most prominently his secure trouble
program to be helpful and answer any
questions I was asked I guess nobody
wanted to restrict who I answer
questions for
probably pretty
pretty then I'd have to help you I mean
it seems pretty obvious Benny wouldn't
want me to but hey not my fault I can't
say no
thanks see you around
recorder
foreign
kind of annoying
I didn't realize my sneak was that I
[Music]
oh
sure he came through here in a big hurry
didn't even stop to say hello I think he
went down his secret
again goal number one is to eliminate Mr
house and install given how you're a new
arrival I also recommend that you get to
know some of the region by the time you
finished up all of that the legion
should be close to attacking Hoover Dam
foreign
hey there's the High Roller
the eyes of the mighty Kaiser are upon
you he appreciates your service and
bestows upon you the exceptional gift of
his mark
my lord requires Your Presence at his
camp at fortification Hill his Mark will
guarantee your safe conduct through our
lands incidentally it will interest you
to know that the man you seek has fled
the strip and is likely making haste for
kaisar's Camp as we speak
seek kaisa by way of Cottonwood Cove
south of Nelson the courser luculus will
be waiting
[Music]
thank you
true to kaisar
what in the world
why in the world is that thing being
blasted at full volume
hold on I have to mute
our way
foreign
I think I might be in the clear for the
moment
foreign
are you rich
the trip will take a few hours
by order of kaisar all visitors must
disarm and relinquish
alcohol and all chems including stims
and
your belongings will be returned
so you're the visitor I've heard some of
the legionaries talking about if you're
in the mood to
have a
give me a shout if you need it
I haven't had the pleasure I have
crossed paths with legged lenius his
second in command however
he's the best the legion has to offer or
so the legionaries say brood of a man
where's a fancy metal mask in a battle
he killed one of my pack brahmins simply
because it was in his way
I knew better than to complain about it
though
no sir
not at all they're my best customers as
long as you don't try to sell them chems
or alcohol they treat you fair
hell I don't even need to travel with
guards most of the time in Legion
territory all the bandits are dead or
run off
between having to hire protection and
getting slapped with taxes it's more
profitable to stick to Arizona and New
Mexico
but I do cross the River from time to
time when opportunity comes along
all right
that's like the thing about
students Legion versus like NCR it's
like oh don't worry about like all the
bands because they're not willing to
like go out and deal with things
but then it's like Allegiance like
overly aggressive and brutal
so what do you deal with
you're slowing down
what the [ __ ] truth what the [ __ ] was
that I've seen crippled slaves move
faster
hi good you
January
oh well I think the game just aren't
crashed
oh oh yeah that's right this area has a
tendency to have really long load times
because there's like a lot of actors
that don't exist when you load in
what's my medical ad I think
yeah 75 should do it for the medical
check is at 70.
waves aren't much of a challenge
Outsiders are a rare sight at the fort
step carefully around here and you might
just leave alive
it took years for Kaiser to conquer
lanius's tribe and kaisar showed Mercy
to the survivors allowing them to join
the legion
had the positions been reversed kaisar
would be dead
lanius is called the monster of the East
because he never ever shows Mercy
been doing it since I was a boy the
mongrels know to listen up when I start
talking to them
we breed them mostly but sometimes we
get some good ones from Denver
that whole city is overrun with them
Lupa
yes she's the mother of a lot of our bet
none may enter without Caesar's
permission
uh-huh some of the slaves have been
spreading stories about the burned man
again
foreign
if you're injured I might have healing
I never finished my training the legion
thought I do know basic first aid but
I've had to rely on tribal remedies to
treat illnesses and I'm always running
low on Xander
oh I've been using two roots for flour
thanks to you
buddy
a small town in New Mexico the legion
three years and counting if I could just
get across the river I'd be free
we're property if you're too young or
too old
I can only do that if you're a friend of
the
the Leggett is not a man to be crossed
I'm looking forward to getting sent
across the river
hold your tongue waste roll
the camps are getting crowded
the new slave girls are quite beautiful
under penalty under penalty of death The
Prisoner is forbidden to speak with you
until
we can talk afterwards
so I finally get to meet The Courier
who's caused so much trouble with the
new California Republic
you spread word of the massacre of
nipton just like wolf has asked you
okay
you turn Camp forlorn hope into a mass
grave I get it we share a common enemy
and now you come before the mighty
Kaiser to what offer your services
maybe I should have you struck blind so
my face is the last sight you ever
behold
look
you do know why I wanted to meet you
right
a man nearly kills you so you track him
across the breath of the Mojave
you arrive on the strip and Waltz into
the Lucky 38 like someone left you a key
under the doormat
you visit the tops and next thing you
know the head of the chairman is fleeing
the strip like a whimpering little pup
when you set your mind to something you
get results
I like that
the question is
are you ready to get started
I have eyes and ears everywhere it
behooves me not to invade the West blind
and deaf
it hasn't been hard to track your
progress it's not as though you've been
keeping a low profile the time is fast
approaching when my Legion will assault
the great dam and invade the West
before that happens I want Mr house
knocked out of the game a quick one-two
punch with you doing the punching
down the hill at the West edge of Camp
is an old building
it was here when the fort was taken in
2277.
inside the building is a hatch
and inside that hatch are two steel
doors that bear the Sigil of the Lucky
38 Casino
now that same sigil is on the Platinum
chip Penny was carrying when we captured
him
isn't that interesting
even more interesting there's a slot
about the same size as the chip on the
console that opens the hatch
so you know what I think
I think the Platinum chip opens those
doors doors that can't be pried open or
drilled open or blasted open
Benny's theory if I understood it
through all the screaming was that Mr
House stashed some kind of Ultimate
Weapon down there
a gigantic robot to stop us all to death
who cares whatever it is house building
so I want it destroyed
I want you to destroy whatever you find
in there and then I want you to come
back here and tell me about it
so go to the building and take this
[ __ ] Platinum chip with you my
legionaries will meet you there with
your weapons and equipment
talk to Benny on your way out he knows
I'm going to let you decide how he dies
maybe you want to remind him
they have to mute my
exiting because I don't have anyone lose
stream dick
rigamaroni's and my key bindings are not
working through the executable in full
screen go
away that we do baby that we do down to
brass tacks how'd your meet and greet
with Baldi go
try not to smile so wide baby you might
break
yeah Baldi said you'd get to decide
yeah to die in my sleep at a ripe old
age after a marathon session of hey hey
with 36 star broads
look I ain't a harbor for illusions I
ain't expecting to get out of this
shindig alive
that's why I'm trying to hand you my
scheme baby it's called having a legacy
you do that for me baby don't tease if
you don't mean it
sure Baldi wants you to go down there in
the bunker and Destroy whatever Mr House
stashed there oh you don't want to do
that baby
whatever's down in that bunker is the
key to the city called Vegas
you go down there and you use the chip
to do whatever Mr house would have
wanted you to do
and when you get back to the strip
I made it so that cat can't help but be
helpful
so you keep saying
the direct approach eh
but you should wait until the bunker is
taken care of she's
which greedy Overlord
Mr House hides Vegas under a skirt when
the bombs fall a thousand years ago so
it belongs to him forever you buy that
baby every boss has a line to explain
why he's special why everyone's got a
Vegas got a swing baby gotta have his
and we covered this
the only thing not bad about them is
they ain't Legion
the NCR is the biggest gang of Thieves
in the Mojave only difference is they
pass laws to make their crimes legal
before they commit them
the chairman
now you're talking that first base is
whatever Mr house would have you do
then when he ain't looking you knock him
out of the running and find a way to
take control of those securitrons of his
go see yes man I made it
nah just Spruce it up with a crucifixion
here and there
the legion is Twisted Baby original
losers worshiping the king of creeps
like he's some kind of God
they're worse than roaches my advice
I'm the most
now in the way back we called ourselves
the boot Riders silly name but that's
how we rode the Mojave dig we were
nomadic badasses not to be trifle with a
gang of Ruffians though with a certain
panache when house gave us the tops to
renovate his robots dropped off boxes
full of suits and ties and wingtip shoes
told us we were the chairman now
that caused an uproar but I said the
name sticks chowed the old ways baby
time to swing in style
seven years
took over three days after Mr House
introduced himself our chief at the time
Mountain of a guy named Bingo wanted to
stay nomadic I disagreed so
he looked so surprised when I stuck that
knife in his neck thought he was so
tough but he was so slow that's how I
made cheap it's how things were back
then
we were east of Vegas when the First
Security we ever saw rolled up on us we
junked it and a minute flat the next day
20 roll up so we listened said we've
been selected Vegas needed us to defend
it in exchange we'd get cushy digs full
stomachs medical treatment everything in
Nomad never gets in other words
I prefer it took every stealth Boy I had
to cross the river at Cottonwood Cove
that was a close shave riding a boat
full of Legion boys once I was across I
changed into a uniform I swiped off a
dead legionary outside Nelson tried to
sneak into the bunker but that didn't
work out they found the chip
I wasn't going to tell them what it was
used for but let's just say
some of the slaves have been spreading
stories about them
oops
none may enter without
Kaiser has permitted your weapons to be
returned
Kaiser has put a lot of trust in you
hold your tongue waste true to Kaiser
well you're here this is where I wanted
you to end up after all I knew I could
rely on Caesar to give you back the
Platinum chip
was that meant to be a shocking
revelation of course Caesar wants it
destroyed he's afraid of what the bunker
might hold and rightly so
but you're not going to do that you're
going to
I don't respond well to threats
the Platinum chip is a data storage
device
I need you to manually upload the data
from the chip to the facility's primary
computer there's a terminal at the other
end of this facility there's a
complication while I can broadcast to
this screen I can't control any of the
facility systems that means I can't
deactivate its security Bots most of
which appear to be active according to
the status board I'm looking at
listen to me very carefully I've waited
too long for this moment for you to go
following it up on a lock
do as I say and your rewards will be
immense
then there will be no
um
I was in a bunch of text screens so I
didn't even remember that I needed to do
that
[Music]
yeah
foreign
thank you
you've carried out kaisar's will but I
must
you're free
I don't think I have any hold on weapons
no at all
way true to kaizard
I felt the ground shake a while ago
there are rewards for doing as I command
today your reward is Vengeance you get
go to Benny let him know what you've
decided my praetorians will perform the
execution
consider it the first of many
bestowments
so baby what did you find down there
what
how could you do that you loser you had
Vegas in the palm of your head
I see and
machetes at 20 Paces hey
you're a Class Act baby not to say I'm
gonna make it easy for you
they hardly even know how to fight
aha
come on
[Music]
damn
they hardly
ah
[Music]
you like that
come on
oh
Let Them Fight themselves
come on
oh
damn
I'm gonna ring your bell creep
y like I said a league they hardly
even know how to fight
I'm sure you found Benny's demise
pleasing the destruction let's press on
shall we
as I was telling you before I want Mr
house out of the picture you have an
interest in his death too if he knows
that you destroyed his gadgets beneath
the fort you know where to find him
how he died
it's called an auto dock as the name
suggests it's an automated physician he
can treat broken bones Cuts puncture
scrapes
makes for a powerful gift in a culture
that forbids painkillers and is largely
ignorant of Medical Science
good
don't know what kind of security he has
inside the Lucky 38
until Mr house has been dealt with you
and I have nothing to talk
uh I don't think it crashed I think it's
just the long loading it says a long
load
true to kaisar Iowa are you ready
foreign
[Music]
slavery
but and you know this thing can move
foreign
wish I could have seen what's inside the
38.
by order of kite
I'm looking forward to getting sent
across the river
foreign
are you okay
at this point the game won the dilemmas
I said you do too much backtracking and
constantly going back here
and the whole disarming thing is kind of
annoying
it is a great honor for anyone outside
the legion to get it
we recently obtained an artillery weapon
but we don't have the
the tribe calling themselves the Boomers
is obsessed with such weapons I've been
he's the best warrior in the legion a
full legionary by the time he was 12.
he's never lost a battle and the leg had
been in command during the Battle of
Hoover Dam the legion would have won I
have no doubt about that
no legit LA News is kaisar second
the Leggett replaced the burned man
after the legion's defeat at the dam
several years ago
the burned man was kaizar's advisor in
general when the legion was originally
formed
the burned man led us to a disastrous on
kaisar's orders the burned man was
covered in Pitch by the praetorian guard
lit on fire and cast into the Grand
Canyon
kaizar has forbidden us from ever
speaking his true name
it's a tradition in the praetorians to
specialize in unarmed combat because
weapons can break or Jam however our
unarmed techniques favor offense over
defense we can charge the enemy and
flatten him with our first strike before
I'll answer if I can
when I was a boy the legion conquered my
I fought in many battles for the legion
eventually kaizar chose me to lead his
praetorian guard
girls and women were enslaved and many
of the men and boys were also choked
we were Savages
the legion raised us up made us
I've read Mr House's obituary
had a high opinion of himself didn't he
with Mr house out of the way I can focus
on smoothing out a few lingering
complications elsewhere in the Mojave
first up are the Boomers of Nellis Air
Force Base
a tribe so reclusive it lobs artillery
shells at anyone who comes near their
settlement I want you to offer them an
alliance with my Legion
my terms are simple
talk and they can keep their freedom
if you find they aren't amenable to this
offer
good your first challenge will be to
reach their settlement without getting
blown up
after that should be easy
hello
any tomatoes to leave screens come on
this instant feeling of like a crash
occurring
whoa there pal you better slow down or
you'll now that I've got your attention
might you be
oh lordy lordy you haven't heard of the
Boomers what rock have you been living
under
there are a bunch of artillery slinging
grenade La Bernard jobs camping out in
Nellis
there is a way
well I know the seat if you make it back
alive I'll double your money
all right I suppose I can cut you a deal
but not a cat okay here you go that page
has the details but it's all in the
timing As you move from building I'll be
here watching so I'll know it's been
forever since I've done it
I need a I need the nudes
foreign
that's actually now here in the past
I'll stick to the High cover in the
north east corner of the two buildings
make a beeline for the game
foreign
how the hell did you survive that
bombardment
but I had you zeroed in the whole time
nope move a muscle now and I'll blow you
to pieces
watch your mouth Savage Raquel be here
I'll take this from here
I'm Raquel Master at Arms for the Nellis
Homeland mother Pearl our
follow close
welcome child
I've been waiting a good
those howitzers of ours aren't just for
entertainment child except you
oh so many ways small ones
should that go well it maybe you can
help and be
you picked a good time to stop by for
we're swimming Raquel could use help
with the bug problem duck Argyle has
wounded he's tending to and loyal and
Jack might be looking for help with some
or you could just go see Pete at the
Museum and hear the story of RP come and
go as you like help
hey
mother Pearl's instructions are clear
you can move freely or these are
extraordinary privilege
long story short the power failed a few
days ago because giant ants have
tunneled into the generator room and set
up a nest
I led a team down to exterminate them
but there were so many of them
personally I think it's more than a
Savage can handle
sure anyone
they exploded when hit by a flamethrower
loyal's been working on some kind of
foreign
[Music]
whoops
thank you
foreign
[Music]
try again
there's no way that should be hitting at
that State
hello outsider
well how about that
bye
good work with those solar
I still
no it doesn't
hello outsider
I don't
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
I still can't believe how you ran
through that artillery barrage
[Music]
I see the powers back on
maybe Pearl is right about you I'll tell
loyal to send someone down to clear out
the eggs
what is it outsider
the next time you leave Nellis keep an
eye out for me
what is it outsider
foreign
you have done well
you may find one in the workshop you're
a friend
I believe the time has come for you to
show your value in full
find loyal and ask him about our
people's fondest dream
foreign
workshop and this guy and Richard firing
mechanism
let's see don't need more of those
anymore this
less of that
more of that
more that
and
let's see here what else
we got
yes
I will
make them all into 44
.
knowing I can't convert them all
let's see what else we got
ta do
oh we gotta get the water going
I have to go and raise a boot from
underneath
Pearl sent word saying it's
I know
so you're the outsider
so I need to go get a
pressure cooker
yeah sorry sometimes I wish you could
just watch right from the inside
speed out
[Music]
foreign
the light is a button that can interrupt
that Nation we were too busy throwing
ourselves to the ground to figure that
out to rearm the mind we just press the
button again simple
thank you
foreign
let's see what the other options are
[Music]
foreign
oops
[Music]
you eyeballing me
come on
probably one down here if I had a guess
hmm
foreign
carefully they got Spies all over
thank you
hey
there back from
thing okay it looks like the valve from
the cooker was a perfect fit
foreign
it's going to be a dream come
that's tremendous I'll transmit
instructions to the robots to start
I just told you the robots are going
ahead
exactly we will be shelling an
unoccupied location in outer Vegas to
get their attention elsewhere
by the time they realize they aren't
under attack the plane and the Bots were
the kids wish we were shelling a real
Target but Pearl thinks it
hello
what you have done you are a truck
of course my child after all that you
have done after all the training and
virtual reality the young ones would
relish an opportunity
foreign
good
I remember this area one of us playing
on PS3 all those years ago
I think I've been playing this game for
almost 10 years
actually probably more than 10 years
as long as I probably started playing in
a 2011 2012.
hey
you must enter Kaisers
have you brought news of the Boomer
good make sure they help the legion when
the time comes as for your next
assignment
I want you to forge an alliance between
kaisar's Legion and the white glove
Society they used to be cannibals I
expect that information can be used to
manipulate
never this
bad before
[ __ ] this
come back
you've proven yourself to be a true
friend of the legion
we have a it's an excellent place to
rest and store extra while he's there
you can acquire items useful for
stealthy operations against
well done
it will be very useful in the coming
battle against the snipers the NCR will
no doubt have hidden in the Hills near
the dam
far away true
foreign
[Music]
but I did anyways
what do you want
I'm here to keep everything in order as
a friend of the Legion I can offer you
some supplies while you're here
I have some Goods collected during my
trout
no there are other places
foreign
[Music]
I'll do this last little bit and
probably close it up
foreign
but could I
did you know the strips all stirred up
lately
humbly At Your Service
here's your
foreign
how may I be of service sir
my such a popular question
the white glove Society has only just
made itself known to the public of
course
where we always so refined
I'd be lying if I said yes
not everyone can wear the finest clothes
and eat the finest food
but surely we can agree that the most
tasteful
ah yes I've heard that one
let me hear your secrets these are great
yes I'm glad you asked I've heard about
you you know
I'm in a bind I've been planning an
Exquisite Society dinner he's got a
powerful and temperamental
yes the wrong person we scouted the
right one for weeks the heir to a
Mercantile Empire sort of a black he cut
ties with his family and left their
estate to wander he was ideal corn fed
and well to do but no one to miss him if
he were to disappear unfortunately the
Trap my subordinate set for him failed
and that
I asked for a last minute replacement
and they stole the son of the most
dangerous Brahmin Baron in New Vegas
well he stayed at this very Hotel
needless to say this could be a disaster
if things aren't put back the way they
should be
strictly speaking we're no longer
allowed to eat people but I'm hoping the
right person in preparation might sway
Marjorie to see things my way
I need a replacement and I need the boy
taken care of the replacement must be
healthy and well bred
with so little time we'll have to go
after our original choice Carlisle
Sinclair he lives in a shack north of
here
if you could send him here or knock him
out with this and drag him into the
dumpster next to his house we can do the
rest
[Music]
not this one empty
I don't believe it's seen you since
before the War and what would the point
be really who would pick up his trash if
he used it but for our purposes it
should keep his body safe and hidden
until my cohorts can recover it
Ted Gunderson is his name it would be
simplest if we could convince him this
was all but if he won't listen we can't
very well let him go he'll have to be
slaughtered and but you would need to
deal with his father heck
splendids the Elder Gunderson is staying
in our Penthouse I understand desired
security so be careful if you go up
there and our Mr Sinclair resides to the
north he rarely stretched
I assume you're joking
no everyone he meets he tells the same
story that his son disappeared from the
casino not from his room he'll look
guilty
indeed
I've heard the legions planning to
unleash their best men against us where
are you boy
dead dead
where are you boy
I must have spent a fortune renovating
this place
good day
hello
Welcome to the ultralux
tell your ruler we have no interest in
such ties Caesar's Legion is a
collection of unclean barbarians
anytime the white glove Society is
as much as Mortimer and some of the
other members have tried to convince me
otherwise I will not have a scene as
Savages
okay
I do but I suppose it is a labor of love
if we at the White Glove Society are all
responsible for maintaining the beauty
and class of the ultralux
and as its founder I suppose it falls to
me to decide how we go about it
foreign
good day
any word as to our arrangement
I see
looking to elevate his social I'll admit
I could see benefits to living under his
rule certain transgress but that's
neither here nor there I'm afraid
Marjorie won't have it
our guys put the monorail back to work
dude
where are you boy
Prim has
it's a new sheriff that should keep the
powder gangers away
howdy
you what do you think you're doing
curse it all your timing couldn't be
more atrocious
just make it quick all right
thank you
there was some kind of massacre at one
of the ranger stations I don't know
which one my daddy's gonna kill all you
bastards once he finds out what you done
my daddy sent you God damn it I almost
died in here what the hell took you so
long who did this to me anyway they hit
me over the head before I got to look at
him
what in the Sam Hell eat I'll tell you
what as soon as I'm out of here and my
daddy knows the story you
to hell with that you've seen those
freaks they dress the same talk the same
you can bet they all eat the same too
they deserve what my dad is going to
have coming for
the hell you
I'm here
[Music]
oh my God it's the most anticlimactic
thing ever
our guys put the monorail
back to work
hey
had enough
[Music]
foreign
oh
good day
those are all members of the white glove
Society are founder Marjorie gave us all
a dress code there's only one rule to it
in her words we must dress in such a way
that no one can be said to have dressed
better than us
as for the masks I'm not allowed to tell
you
actually that's not true that's just
what we're supposed to say I think
Marjorie likes them for the mystery they
create and the way they make it clear
that we're different from everyone else
but you didn't hear that from me
must have forgotten to put it on
I'm not really gambling I'm just hoping
to be
in here people will think I'm rich
what is it says
you've done the right thing citizen
reporting struggles scuffles and tussles
thanks to you we can all sleep in our
beds a little Sounder knowing that Swift
Justice awaits those who take moral
shortcuts for personal gain rest assured
I will apprehend the perpetrator and see
him or her punished even though it's
someone
I'm out of here
beg your pardon
you're under arrest
that's my son you're talking about he
ain't dead I'm looking for him it is my
duty to inform you that murder is a
serious crime
as a murderer you should be feeling
emotions such as guilt sorrow and shame
if not you may wish to consult a mental
health professional
where's my son what'd you do with my boy
I hope this experience has taught you an
important lesson about the value of
human life
you can't do this to me this is a
mistake please allow me to escort you to
the nearest criminal processing facility
deceased bodies are a known source of
illness
with house out of the way I hope someone
opens a lucky 38.
any word is to our arrangement
so the baron has slaughtered his last
brunt how delightful he was a pox on our
business
he would have driven the price of beef
down to the point where any poor wretch
could afford it can you imagine but now
we can price it even higher create a new
luxury Market not for you of course
you'll get a special discount
we'll know after tonight's banquet at
seven o'clock
I'll only be telling everyone what
they've eaten after they've eaten it
that way they will all have crossed the
same silly taboo they'll have to
reconsider it even Marjorie
it's all image with her anyway
she just needs to realize the only
difference between
to think Mr but his arrest ought to
instill faith in our patrons that
murderers are not welcome to gamble here
tell your
ah you're back
we'll know after tonight's banquet at
seven that way they will all have
crossed the same silly taboo
it's all image with her
ah you're back
we'll know after tonight's banquet at
seven o'clock that way
it's all image
I'd wager that the Army's sending a leap
had enough
thank you
I'm here
foreign
[Music]
you're back
I certainly did Philippe created an
extraordinary amused bush from the Flesh
of the Gunderson boy
everyone at the bank would loved it I
told him what it was and the room was
quiet for a moment but then we all had a
hearty laugh
now that it's been accepted it will
become a regular course for us
it's a new and exciting front
oh I very much doubt that then again I
wouldn't be surprised if our Chef used
it here and there as a secret ingredient
to
I should think so but it would be I have
however told her how instrumental you
were in revolutionizing our Cuisine and
she knows what we stand to gain from a
ruler who supports it have a word with
her see which
things are getting stranger every day
what can I get
you thanks
salutations
I've heard you have to make reservations
at the Gourmand years in advance
ah you're back
must do stuff
welcome to the Ultra Lux
why it's Splendid Mortimer told me about
you you know what a pair of Mischief
Makers you two are
but the new entrees are fresh and bold
and I have
I don't care for their incivility or the
hodgepodge of sporting equipment that
passes for fashion with them
nevertheless
I have heard Caesar has a stately
dignity about him
and I understand his policies will agree
with our new menu
I prefer Mr House of course but he may
not be around forever and the NCR will
surely set back our cuisine
to
I've heard that elite units are on the
way to support our armies here
howdy come try your luck I hope it's on
your side
foreign
by order of cut
hey
true to kaisar
the last time we met I believe we were
talking about the white glove Society
I appreciate your concern but I'm in
excellent health
and we have other matters to discuss
have you been successful in your efforts
to recruit the white glove Society
good
it will be valuable to have allies on
the Strip when Hoover Dam is taken
now as for your next assignment I want
you to destroy the Mojave chapter of the
Brotherhood of Steel
it's not a full-strength chapter mind
you the profligates
um
uh yeah
the Brotherhood
I don't I don't know
there have been a couple
don't but
just leave it alone I'm fine look for
the brotherhood's bunker around
I'm going to bed we'll talk
laid girls
are beautiful
neat
all right so probably about this finish
up this run and I think I'll probably
start another character that's more
melee focused alongside the multiplayer
mod
just to give something something to do
in the afternoons
hang up with the exit until I get out of
this